We're going to be on a tight schedule
this time, so be ready for that.
Yes, ma'am! I'll give it my all.
It's beautiful!
NAHA AIRPORT - DOMESTIC
It's a pleasure to be working with you all.
Let's head to the filming
location right away.
We'll carpool there with
our provided vehicle.
It's gorgeous here.
It really is.
I'm glad it's sunny.
Right? It was raining just before.
Yeah. Now I'm feeling pumped!
- Yeah!
- Uh-huh!
We're here.
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
"The Really Hot Okinawa Business Trip!"
Yeah, that's good!
Nice!
Looking good!
Look up at the sky a bit.
Okay.
I think that covers this spot.
They'll let us take videos of them
during their break later, right?
Correct.
We've discussed the behind-the-scenes
content with them already.
Just be sure to let them know
so you can record them.
Understood.
By the way...
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
It's one thing for Nashiko Akitsuki-san...
but why are you also in a swimsuit, Senpai?
Akitsuki-san is wearing a swimsuit!
It'd be rude if we didn't do the same!
Oh, but... I don't think that's
really necessary... is it?
Is that... so?
It's her job to wear hers, so...
Really?
No, my apologies!
I don't really know the proper etiquette
for a swimsuit photoshoot, either.
Oh! My hat!
Senpai?
Thank you so much.
No problem.
Senpai!
- Here's a towel.
- I'm fine.
This will dry off in no time.
See? Good thing I wore a swimsuit!
You're right!
- Then I'll wear a swimsuit from now on, too.
- Yeah!
Why am I getting all excited like a kid?
How immature of me!
Thanks for your help today, you two.
The pleasure is ours.
You've coordinated so many things for us.
By the way, that swimsuit
looks great on you!
You're in great shape, too.
Do you do any training to get that physique?
No, not really.
Really?
Your arms are so slim.
Excuse me! Um...
Nashiko Akitsuki-san's on her break now,
so we should go check on her.
Oh, you're right.
I'll go get them their refreshments,
so you two go on ahead.
Will do!
Now, let's ask them to check the footage—
Thanks.
Oh. No problem.
Why have I been feeling so uneasy?
What a great spot!
It's so pretty!
Well, let's get going!
FREE PARKING
Ow, that's cold!
Here. You need to drink, too.
Thank you.
You've been working so hard.
Er, I mean...
B-Be sure to drink the whole thing!
Good work on our first day of photoshoots!
Good work!
Wow, this really was a great place to shoot!
The weather's great,
and everything's running on schedule!
It's all thanks to Kannawa-san's
management skills!
Absolutely!
I'm really grateful!
No, no. I'm grateful for you all, as well.
And thank you, Kamegawa-san.
You've been so helpful.
Oh, not at all.
I still have a lot to learn.
Hello, all! Welcome!
Enjoying your evening here in Okinawa?
Oh! Live folk songs!
Now, then!
Let's all do the Kachashi dance!
The men do "rock,"
and the women do "paper."
Sounds fun! Let's dance!
All right!
Come on, you guys too,
Kannawa-san and Kamegawa-san!
Huh? Uh, no, I...
Why's this happenin'?
I'd rather be publicly executed!
- Well, shall we go dance?
- Huh?
Do a "rock" with both hands and...
Wait... Huh? This is hard...
You look like you're doing an Obon dance.
It's all good as long as I'm having fun.
I need to get it together.
I'm sullying my senpai title if I can't
even dance when my own junior is!
Okay!
- Like this?
- Yeah!
I'm beat!
Thanks.
Why do I feel uneasy?
Coming.
Senpai?
Sorry for showing up unannounced.
It's okay. Anything wrong?
- Here. For you.
- Huh?
Haven't you noticed?
You're seriously sunburned.
Whoa. You're right.
Come to think of it,
I didn't put on any sunscreen.
I thought so.
We're doing PR for sunscreen, remember?
- You should be ashamed.
- I'm sorry.
It might be May,
but the rays in Okinawa are... y'know...
I'll put it on tomorrow for sure.
Thank you very much.
Yeah.
Well, goodnight.
Goodnight.
FORTUNE
That concludes the photoshoots.
Good work.
Good job, everyone.
Thank you so much!
We were able to work smoothly
thanks to everyone's efforts.
The rest of the afternoon
will be free time.
This is the first time I've had
free time on a photoshoot day!
Right?
I'm glad we finished without any issues.
But free time, huh?
What'll Kamegawa do?
Should we go somewhere together?
No, I'm sure a junior wouldn't like
to be invited by his senior.
I wonder what Senpai's going to do.
Would you all like to go
sightseeing together?
Oh! I like that idea!
I'm down!
You two will join us, right?
Um...
We had such a great
time last night, after all!
Yup!
Wh-What do I do?
To be honest, I used up my nonexistent
communication skills yesterday and today.
I'm at my limit!
No, this is the time for me to push through!
Once I get through this, we get to go home!
Then let's—
Excuse me, Senpai!
Um...
Oh, yeah! The collab café!
There's a different place
I wanted to suggest for it, and...
Oh! Is that so?
I-It's true!
In that case, the two of you should split off.
I'll take your bigger luggage to our bus.
I wish you luck with your work!
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry to make you stick with me.
No, you helped me out there.
So what café were you thinking of going to?
L-Let me look it up right now!
"Naha." "Café."
Wow, there are so many...
Oh, this one looks good.
You're right!
Every café was so nice.
You could really feel the
charm of Okinawa in them.
I learned a lot.
Agreed.
Senpai, thank you for everything,
from yesterday to today.
He really takes his work seriously.
I'm sure it was tough,
but he didn't complain one bit.
Well, that's a given since it's work,
after all. But still...
Did he get to enjoy himself,
even just a little?
Senpai?
Oh, just...
We were able to get footage without
any issues thanks to your support.
Thanks.
Good work!
Kannawa-san! Kamegawa-san!
What? Is that true?
What's the matter?
The rooms...
We might only have one reserved.
What?!
Looks like you only have
the one twin room reserved.
What's going on?!
I definitely asked for two separate rooms!
PROPOSAL FOR THE NEW SUNSCREEN LINE
Let's go get lunch, Tama-chan.
Okie-dokie! Let's go right now!
Hey, listen to this.
TWIN (TWO BEDS)
I was asked to arrange a hotel,
and it's so hard!
Are there any other rooms available?
I'm terribly sorry.
All rooms are currently booked
due to Golden Week.
Of course.
Senpai...
Let's just put our stuff away
and go take a bath!
We'll figure things out from there.
Understood!
This is the first time I've felt so anxious
while bathing in an outdoor bath.
Even if it's twin beds,
we'll be sharing the same room.
He's definitely going to be nervous.
Should I find a room at a different hotel?
No, not at this hour. Plus it's Golden Week.
Wait a minute...
Don't I attract too much bad luck?
There was a time I had to share
a room with Kanzaki-senpai, too!
Kanna... Looks like we're sharing rooms.
O-Okay! As long as it's no trouble for you!
Let's go eat something tasty and expense it.
Is it weird for me to be this worried about it?
I'm just his senior, and he's just my junior...
What to do?
Huh?
Oh! I'm sorry.
I was replying to work emails.
- I'll leave right now.
- Huh?
I'll spend the night at a nearby
manga café or something. So don't worry.
Wait a minute!
Why would you do that?
I'm sure you won't be able to
rest very well with me in here.
I'll meet you in the lobby tomorrow morning.
- See you then.
- Hey!
I've had something like this
happen before, so it's not an issue!
Huh?
These kinds of things... you know...
happen a lot.
What I'm trying to say is that
you don't need to worry.
Y-You're right.
Of course it's possible.
Yup!
It was fun when I stayed with
my senpai, whom I looked up to!
Oh, but... that doesn't mean you
should force yourself to have fun.
Actually, I'll head out.
Let me challenge you again!
Huh? Oh...
- But...
- Enough!
Or what? Are you...
scared of losing to me?
Did you forget that you couldn't win
a single round last time, Senpai?
Ugh! I can't turn the corners fast enough!
But you've improved a lot
since last time, Senpai!
OKINAWA GOYA CHIPS
Go!
Yes!
I lost again.
What's with your sudden speed boost
right before the goal? You're cheating!
I'm not cheating.
Oh, are you using the turbo skill, Senpai?
The tur... what?
This gauge on the bottom right.
It charges up when you drift.
When it maxes out, press it.
You'll accelerate at an explosive speed.
Wow, I had no idea!
Now I'll win for sure!
- Maybe.
- Hey...
- Huh?
- Your cheeks are red from your sunburn.
No, this is...
Did you put on sunscreen?
I even went out of my way to give you some.
- I'm going to go buy a drink.
- Okay.
EMERGENCY EXIT
What was that back there?
It was fun when I stayed with my
senpai, whom I looked up to!
Whoever it was, I'm sure they were
a lot more reliable than me.
I, on the other hand, just make Senpai worry.
I'm jealous of them...
I'm back.
Oh, well.
You're late!
How long were you going to make me wait?!
What?! You were sound asleep just now!
I'm not sleeping 'til I win!
Now get ready!
Roger that!
We'll barely make it.
We'll make it if we hustle!
Never thought think we'd compete like that.
But thanks to that, I've come up with
a lot of ideas for the collab café's menu.
Visiting all those cafés
was really productive, too.
Okinawa was so much fun, right?
Yeah, it was!
But when we get back, be prepared
for a schedule from hell. Got it?
I-I'll do my best!